A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, Grants, Accessions 2014-2015, RG 3 FA763
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, Grants, 1970-2012; 3.3; 43.2 Cubic Feet 95 standard document storage boxes 3 legal size document storage boxes Boxes 1-98
  - Association for the Forum on Non-Governmental Initiatives, 1999-2002
  - Association of Governing Boards of Universities Colleges, 1987-1990, 1993-1995 (Box 82, Folder 445-447)
  - Association of Hispanic Arts, Inc., 2003-2004, 2006 (Box 83, Folder 448)
  - Association for Innovative Cooperation in Europe, 1987-1996
  - Association for Innovative Cooperation in Europe, 1987-1996 (Box 84, Folder 453-454)
  - Association for Innovative Cooperation in Europe, Tax Information, 1985-1988, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 455)
  - Association for Neighborhood and Housing Development, Inc., 2004-2006
  - Association for Research on Nonprofit Organizations and Voluntary Action (ARNOVA), 1989, 1991, 1996-2002 (Box 84, Folder 457-458)
  - Association for Research on Nonprofit Organizations and Voluntary Action (ARNOVA), 1989, 1991, 1996-2002 (Box 85, Folder 459-462)
  - Association of Small Foundations, 1996-2003
  - Association of Small Foundations, 1996-2003 (Box 86, Folder 464-166)
  - Atlantic Council of the United States, Inc., 1988-1996, 2000 (Box 86, Folder 467-468)
  - Atlantic Council of the United States, Inc., 1988-1996, 2000 (Box 87, Folder 469-473)
  - Atlantic Council of the United States, Inc., Tax Information, 1970-1973, 1976, 1978, 1988-1992, 1994-1995 (Box 87, Folder 474)
  - Atlantic Council of the United States, Joint Study of American Policy Toward China, 1991-1995 (Box 88, Folder 475-479)
  - Atlantic Council of the United States, Joint Study of American Policy Toward China, 1991-1995 (Box 89, Folder 480)
  - Auburn University, 2001-2002, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 481)
  - Audubon Partnership for Economic Development Corporation, 1999-2000 (Box 89, Folder 482)
  - Australian Association of Philanthropy, 1992-1994 (Box 89, Folder 483)
  - Australian Council for Overseas Aid, 1995-1997 (Box 89, Folder 484)
  - The Australian National University, 1986-1997 (Box 89, Folder 485-486)
  - The Australian National University, 1986-1997 (Box 90, Folder 487-492)
  - The Australian National University, 1986-1997 (Box 91, Folder 493-497)
  - The Australian National University, Tax Information, 1984-1985, 1988-1990, 1992-1994 (Box 92, Folder 498-499)
  - B 92 Fund, 2005-2006 (Box 92, Folder 500)
  - BBB Wise Giving Alliance, 1970-1979, 1986, 1988, 1990-1992, 1995, 1997, 1999-2007
  - BBB Wise Giving Alliance, 1970-1979, 1986, 1988, 1990-1992, 1995, 1997, 1999-2007 (Box 93, Folder 504-505)
  - BEC New Communities Housing Development Fund Company, Inc., 1993-1994 (Box 93, Folder 506)
  - Badi Foundation, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 507)
  - The George Balanchine Foundation, Inc., 2005-2006 (Box 93, Folder 508)
  - Balkan Community Initiatives Trust, 2001-2006
  - Balkan Investigative Reporting Regional Network, 2006-2008 (Box 94, Folder 511)
  - Balkan Sunflowers USA, 2007, 2009 (Box 94, Folder 512)
  - Balkans Youth Link-Albania, 2004-2006 (Box 94, Folder 513)
  - Ballet Hispanico of New York, 2005-2008
  - The Bank Information Center, 1997-2005
  - The Bank Information Center, 1997-2005 (Box 95, Folder 518-520)
  - Bank Street College of Education, 1990, 1993, 1995-2000, 2002-2003
  - Bank Street College of Education, 1990, 1993, 1995-2000, 2002-2003 (Box 96, Folder 524-526)
  - Bank Street College of Education, 1990, 1993, 1995-2000, 2002-2003
  - Barnard College, 1993-1994, 1996, 1999 (Box 96, Folder 527-528)
  - Gerald O. Barney & Associates, Inc., 1983-1987 (Box 96, Folder 529)
  - Gerald O. Barney & Associates, Inc., 1983-1987 (Box 97, Folder 530)
  - Stefan Batory Foundation, 1990-1993, 1995-1996, 2000-2005 (Box 97, Folder 531-533)
  - Barrow Group, Inc., 2002, 2004-2005
  - Battery Dance Corporation, 2003-2005 (Box 97, Folder 535)
  - Vivian Beaumont Theater, Inc., 1999-2000, 2006-2009 (Box 98, Folder 536)
  - Vivian Beaumont Theater, Inc., 1999-2000, 2006-2009 (Box 98, Folder 536A)
  - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, 2006-2008 (Box 98, Folder 537)
- Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, Grants, 1968-2013; 3.4; 14.4 Cubic Feet 32 letter size boxes 1 legal size box 1 -1/2 letter box
  - Beijer Institute, 1986-1990 (Box 98, Folder 538-540)
    - Beijer Institute (Folder 538) - Climate Change Volume 15 nos. 1-2 October 1989 - Published Material, 1990; 2014:031:020 (Item 2014:031:020)
  - Beijer Institute, 1986-1990 (Box 99, Folder 541-546)
  - Beijer Institute, Tax Information, 1986-1990 (Box 100, Folder 547)
  - Beijing Chaoyang District Yongxu Global Environmental Institute, 2007-2009 (Box 100, Folder 548)
  - Belgrade Fund for Political Excellence, 2004-2008 (Box 100, Folder 549)
  - Belgrade Fund for Political Excellence, Tax Information, 2004-2008 (Box 100, Folder 550)
  - Beneficial to the Public Fund, 1994-1998 (Box 100, Folder 551-552)
  - Beneficial to the Public Fund, 1994-1998 (Box 101, Folder 553-558)
    - Beneficial to the Public Fund, 1995
      4 oversized architectural drawings
  - Beneficial to the Public Fund, Tax Information, 1994-1997 (Box 101, Folder 559)
  - Benton Foundation, 1999-2001, 2003-2004 (Box 102, Folder 560-561)
  - Better World Society, 1988-1991 (Box 102, Folder 562)
  - Big Shoes Foundation, 2008-2009 (Box 102, Folder 563)
  - Big Sky Institute for the Advancement of Nonprofits, 2002-2003, 2006, 2008-2009 (Box 102, Folder 564)
  - The Biodiversity Project, Inc., 2004-2006 (Box 102, Folder 565)
  - Bishop Museum, 1989-1993, 1995, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 566-568)
  - BoardSource, 1990-2007, 2009 (Box 103, Folder 569-570)
  - BoardSource, 1990-2007, 2009 (Box 103, Folder 569A)
  - BoardSource, 1990-2007, 2009 (Box 104, Folder 571-576)
  - BoardSource, 1990-2007, 2009 (Box 105, Folder 577-582)
  - BoardSource, 1990-2007, 2009 (Box 106, Folder 583-584)
  - BoardSource, Tax Information, 1990-2002, 2004-2006 (Box 106, Folder 585)
  - The Body Shop Foundation, 2004-2005 (Box 106, Folder 586)
  - Bogor Agriculture Universty, 1999-2001 (Box 106, Folder 587)
  - Boston Foundation, 1988-1992 (Box 106, Folder 588-590)
  - Boston Foundation, 1989-1992 (Box 107, Folder 591-595)
  - Boston University, 2000-2002 (Box 107, Folder 596)
  - Botanical Research Institute of Texas, 1992-1998 (Box 107, Folder 597)
  - Botswana Development Corporation, 1972-1975, 1988 (Box 108, Folder 598)
  - Brazilian Institute of Social and Economic Analyses, 2004-2005 (Box 108, Folder 599)
  - Breakthrough Technologies Institute, Inc., 2004 (Box 108, Folder 600)
  - William J. Brennan, Jr. Center for Justice, Inc., 2002-2009 (Box 108, Folder 601)
  - William J. Brennan, Jr. Center for Justice, Inc., 2002-2009 (Box 108, Folder 602-605)
  - William J. Brennan, Jr. Center for Justice, Inc., 2002-2009 (Box 109, Folder 606-611)
  - William J. Brennan, Jr. Center for Justice, Inc., 2002-2009 (Box 110, Folder 612-615)
  - William J. Brennan,, Jr. Center for Justice, Inc., Tax Information, 2002, 2004-2008 (Box 110, Folder 616)
  - Bridge Initiative International, 2005-2008 (Box 110, Folder 617)
  - Bridge Initiative International, 2005-2008 (Box 110, Folder 618)
  - Bridge Initiative International, 2005-2008 (Box 111, Folder 619)
  - Bridge Initiative International, Tax Information, 2005-2008 (Box 111, Folder 620)
  - Bridgespan Group, 1999-2000, 2002, 2004 (Box 111, Folder 621)
  - Bronx Council on the Arts, Inc., 2003-2008 (Box 111, Folder 622)
    - Bronx Council on the Arts, Inc., 2008
      "Restricted - Open in 2019"
      CD-Journey to the Stage, Jen Shyu and Muhamadou Suso Perform, 2008 March 9
    - Bronx Council on the Arts, Inc.
      Scope and Contents
      Artisans Initiative
  - Bronx Council on the Arts, Inc., 2003-2008 (Box 111, Folder 623-624)
  - Bronx Council on the Arts, Inc., 2003-2008 (Box 112, Folder 625)
  - Bronx Museum of the Arts, 2007-2009 (Box 112, Folder 626-627)
  - The Brookings Institution, 1985-2000, 2002-2009 (Box 112, Folder 628)
  - The Brookings Institution, 1985-2000, 2002-2009 (Box 112, Folder 629-630)
  - The Brookings Institution, 1985-2000, 2002-2009 (Box 113, Folder 631-636)
  - The Brookings Institution, 1985-2000, 2002-2009 (Box 114, Folder 637-642)
  - The Brookings Institution, 1985-2000, 2002-2009 (Box 115, Folder 643-646)
  - The Brookings Institution, Tax Information, 1972, 1975-1982, 1984-1955, 2002-2008 (Box 115, Folder 647-648)
  - The Brookings Institution, Tax Information, 1972, 1975-1982, 1984-1955, 2002-2008 (Box 115, Folder 647A)
  - Brooklyn Academy of Music (BAM) Local Development Corporation, 2002-2007 (Box 116, Folder 649-650)
  - Brooklyn Academy of Music (BAM) Local Development Corporation, 2002-2007 (Box 116, Folder 649A-650A)
  - The Brooklyn Academy of Music, Inc., 2000-2007 (Box 116, Folder 651-653)
  - The Brooklyn Academy of Music, Inc., 2000-2007 (Box 116, Folder 651A)
  - The Brooklyn Academy of Music, Inc., 2000-2007 (Box 117, Folder 654-655)
  - The Brooklyn Academy of Music, Inc., 2000-2007 (Box 117, Folder 655A)
  - Brooklyn Arts Council, 2007-2009 (Box 117, Folder 656)
  - Brooklyn Arts Exchange, Inc., 2005-2007 (Box 117, Folder 657)
  - Brooklyn Arts Exchange, Inc., 2005-2007 (Box 117, Folder 657A)
  - Brooklyn Bridge Park Conservancy, Inc., 1999-2008 (Box 117, Folder 658-660)
  - Brooklyn Bridge Park Conservancy, Inc., 1999-2008 (Box 117, Folder 658A)
  - Brooklyn Bridge Park Conservancy, Inc., 1999-2008 (Box 117, Folder 660A)
  - Brooklyn Bureau of Community Services, 2001-2003 (Box 118, Folder 661)
  - Brooklyn Children's Museum Corporation, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 662)
  - Brooklyn Historical Society, 1992-1994, 2006-2007 (Box 118, Folder 663-664)
  - Brooklyn Historical Society, 1992-1994, 2006-2007 (Box 118, Folder 663A)
  - Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences, 1990-1995 (Box 118, Folder 665-667)
  - Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences, 1990-1995 (Box 119, Folder 668-670)
  - Brooklyn Philharmonic Symphony Orchestra, 2002, 2008, 2010-2013 (Box 119, Folder 671)
    "Restricted - Open in 2024"
  - Brooklyn Philharmonic Symphony Orchestra, 2002-2008, 2010-2013 (Box 119, Folder 672-673)
  - Brooklyn Philharmonic Symphony Orchestra, 2002-2008, 2010-2013 (Box 119, Folder 673A)
  - Brooklyn Waterfront Artists Coalition, Inc., 2003-2004, 2006-2007 (Box 120, Folder 674)
    - Brooklyn Waterfront Artist Coalition, Inc., 2006
      2015:006:004, CD-Transformations, Pier Show 14
    - Brooklyn Waterfront Artist Coalition, Inc., 2006
      2015:006:005, CD-Food For...A Feast for the Eyes
    - Brooklyn Waterfront Artist Coalition, Inc., 2006 September 30-October 29
      2015:006:006, CD-Experimentation, BWAC Fall Group Show
  - Brooklyn Waterfront Artists Coalition, Inc., 2003-2004, 2006-2007 (Box 120, Folder 675-676)
  - Brown University, 1988-1993, 1995-1996, 2005-2009, 2012 (Box 120, Folder 677-679)
  - Brown University, 1988-1993, 1995-1996, 2005-2009, 2012 (Box 120, Folder 677A)
  - Brown University, 1988-1993, 1995-1996, 2005-2009, 2012 (Box 121, Folder 680-683)
  - Brown University, 1988-1993, 1995-1996, 2005-2009, 2012 (Box 121, Folder 683A)
  - Bryant Park Restoration Corporation, 1979-1994 (Box 121, Folder 684)
  - Budapest University of Economic Sciences, 1985-1986, 1988-1995 (Box 122, Folder 685-686)
  - The Burnham Institute, 2001-2002 (Box 122, Folder 687)
  - Business Council for International Understanding, Inc., 2005-2007 (Box 122, Folder 688)
  - Business Human Rights Resource Centre US Ltd., 2006-2008 (Box 122, Folder 689)
  - Business-Higher Education Forum, 1990-1993 (Box 122, Folder 690)
  - Business-Higher Education Forum, 1990-1993 (Box 123, Folder 691-692)
  - CAB International, 2001-2005 (Box 123, Folder 693-696)
  - CAB International, 2001-2005 (Box 124, Folder 697)
  - CAF, Inc., 1989-1994 (Box 124, Folder 698-702)
  - CAF, Inc., 1989-1994 (Box 125, Folder 703-707)
  - CAF, Inc., 1989-1994 (Box 126, Folder 708)
  - CAF, Inc., Tax Information, 1971-1974, 1981-1986, 1988, 1990 (Box 126, Folder 709)
  - CAF, Inc., Corporate-By-Laws, 1968-1970, 1972-1973 (Box 126, Folder 710)
  - CEC Stuyvesant Cove, Inc., 2006-2007 (Box 126, Folder 711)
    - CEC Stuyvesant Cove, Inc., 2007 June 7
      2015:006:007, DVD: Solar 2 CAD Model and Promotional Video
  - CEE Bankwatch Network, 1998-2003 (Box 126, Folder 712-713)
  - CEE Bankwatch Network, 1998-2003 (Box 127, Folder 714-716)
  - CEE Bankwatch Network, Tax Information, 1997-2004 (Box 127, Folder 717)
  - CNA Corporation, 2006-2007, 2009-2010 (Box 127, Folder 718)
  - CODEL, Inc., 1976-1977, 1979, 1983, 1987-1988 (Box 127, Folder 719)
  - California Institute of Public Affairs, 1994-1996 (Box 128, Folder 720)
  - The California States Colleges, Sacramento, 1982 (Box 128, Folder 721)
  - University of California, Tax Information, 1970, 1975, 1983-1984, 1986-1988, 1990, 1992-1993, 1997-1998, 2000-2003, 2006-2007 (Box 128, Folder 722)
  - University of California, Berkeley, 1986-1994, 1997, 2005-2009 (Box 128, Folder 723)
  - University of California, Berkeley, 1986-1994, 1997, 2005-2009 (Box 128, Folder 724-725)
  - University of California, Berkeley, 1986-1994, 1997, 2005-2009 (Box 128, Folder 724A)
  - University of California, Berkeley, 1986-1994, 1997, 2005-2009 (Box 129, Folder 726-729)
  - University of California, Davis, 2002 (Box 129, Folder 730)
  - University of California, Irvine, 1986, 2001-2004 (Box 129, Folder 731)
  - University of California, Los Angeles, 1986-1992, 1995, 2000-2004, 2006 (Box 129, Folder 732-733)
  - University of California, Los Angeles, 1986-1992, 1995, 2000-2004, 2006 (Box 129, Folder 733A)
  - University of California, Los Angeles, 1986-1992, 1995, 2000-2004, 2006 (Box 130, Folder 734-739)
    - International Nuclear Trade and Nonproliferation; The Challenge of the Emerging suppliers, by William C. Potter. ISBN:0-6669-21120-6, 2015:016:001 (Item 2015:016:001)
  - University of California, Los Angeles, 1986-1992, 1995, 2000-2004, 2006 (Box 130, Folder 734A)
  - University of California, Los Angeles, 1986-1992, 1995, 2000-2004, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 740-741)
  - University of California, San Diego, 1983, 1999-2003, 2005 (Box 131, Folder 472)
  - University of California, San Diego, Graduate School of International Relations and Pacific Studies, 1992-1996 (Box 131, Folder 743)
  - University of California, San Diego, Institute on Global Conflict and Cooperation, 1994-1996 (Box 131, Folder 744)
  - University of California, San Diego, Institute on Global Conflict and Cooperation, 1994-1996 (Box 132, Folder 745)